Guide to the Daniel Rubin Papers TAM.657
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
Daniel Rubin Papers
1930s-2012
TAM.657
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
142.0 linear feet
Rubin, Daniel, 1931-
Rubin, Daniel, 1931-
- Audiotapes
  - Joann Watson, circa 1991 (Box 1)
  - N/C 28B, 29B, Jan 1991 (Box 1)
  - Gus Hall Update, Mar 20, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Economics Not Really Marxist, undated (Box 1)
  - N/C 28A and 29B, Jan 1991 (Box 1)
  - National Public Radio, "All Things Considered", Sep 20, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Gus Hall Update, Apr 16, 1991 (Box 1, Box Shared Access Tam Box 1)
  - National Committee, Jan 27, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Gus Hall Update, Sep 5, 1989 (Box Shared Access Tam Box 1, Box 1)
  - Gus Hall Update, Apr 2, 1991 (Box Shared Access Tam Box 1, Box 1)
  - N/C 26A and 27A, Jan 1991 (Box 1, Box Shared Access Tam Box 1)
  - Gus Hall - Draft Report, undated (Box 1, Box Shared Access Tam Box 1)
  - Tape 2 Program Comm. Jim J., Danny Rubin, Mar 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape II Program Comm. Side A: Mike Disc. Stra. Barry Disc. Stra. Side B: Barry Disc. Stra. Jim S. Disc. Stra., Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape XV Program Comm. Side A: Procedure Ends 2/3 Through Tape, Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape III Program Comm. Side A: Jim S. Disc. Stra. Lou Disc. Stra. Side B: Lou Disc. Stra. Scottie on W.C., Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape V Program Comm. Side A: Charlene Disc. W.C. Tim J. on Afro. Side B: Tim J. on Afro. Jim S. Disc. Afro., Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape I Program Comm. Side A: Org. Jim J. Strategy Side B: Jim J. on Stra. Jarvis on Stra. Mike Disc. Stra., Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape VII Program Comm. Side A: Charlene on Peace Tom F. on Peace Jim J. Disc. Peace Side B: Jim J. Peace Kendra Disc. Peace, Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape X Program Comm. Side A: Lou on Socialism Jim J. Disc. Socio. Side B: Charlene Disc. Socialism Kendra Disc. Socio., Dec 1990 (Box Shared Access Tam Box 1, Box 1)
  - XI Program Comm. Kendra-Socialism Lou Disc. Socialism, Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - XII Program Comm. Side A: Democracy-Jim S., Barry Side B: Jim J. Disc. Democracy Ends with Charlene Disc. Democracy, Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape I Jim Jackson Program Comm Opening, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape XI Program Comm. Kendra-Lou Dis. Socialism, Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Program Comm. Ends 2 Thirds Through Procedure, Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape IV Program Comm. Side A: Scottie and Danny on W.C. Jarvis Disc. W.C. Side B: Jarvis Disc. W.C. Charlene Disc. W.C., Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape V Program Comm. Side A: Charlene Disc. W.C. Tim J. on Afro. Side B: Tim J. on Afro. Rick on Afro. Jim S. Disc. Afro, Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape IX Program Comm. Side A: Fern on Women Danny Disc. Women Side B: Danny Disc. Women Lou on Socialism, Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape VIII Program Comm. Side A: Kendra Disc. Peace Danny on Nat'l Oppres. Kendra Disc. N.O. Side B: Kendra Disc. Nat'l Oppr. Fern on Women, Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape VI Program Comm. Side A: Scottie on Afro. Lorenzo on Afro. Side B: Lorenzo Disc. Afro. Charlene on Peace, Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape XIV Program Comm. Side A: Barry Disc. Pty. Lou Disc. Pty. Side B: Jim S. Disc. Pty. Kentra Concl. on Pty.; Procedure, Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Tape XIII Program Comm. Side A: Charlene Disc. Demo. Side B: Ends Kendra on Pty. Barry Starts Disc., Dec 1990 (Box 1)
  - Anti-Monopoly Strategy IA, undated (Box 1)
  - Anti-Monopoly Strategy 2A, undated (Box 1)
  - Workshop #5 Nationally Oppressed People Tape I, undated (Box 1)
  - Workshop #5 Nationally Oppressed People Tape II, undated (Box 1)
  - Struggle for Women's Equality 1 and 2, undated (Box 1)
  - Struggle for Women's Equality #3, undated (Box 1)
  - Workshop #17 Reaching the Millions Tape I, undated (Box 1)
  - Workshop #17 Reaching the Millions Tape II, undated (Box 1)
  - Tape 1 USA Socialism Workshop Ideological Conference #14, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Tape 2 USA Socialism Workshop Ideological Conference, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Workshop #14 US Socialism Tape II Sides 3 and 4, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Working Class Workshop I 130-150 Part Erased, undated (Box 2)
  - Working Class Workshop II, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #10 Struggle for Democracy Tape II, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #16 Tape I The Party A, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #16 Tape II The Party A, undated (Box 2)
  - Youth Tape 1 Sides A and B, undated (Box 2)
  - Youth Tape 2 Sides A and B (Box 2)
  - Mexican-American Workshop I, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #10 Struggle for Democracy Tape I, undated (Box 2)
  - Working Class Workshop I Ideological Conference, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Workshop #9 Global Problems Tape I, undated (Box 2)
  - African-American Equality I, undated (Box 2)
  - African-American Equality II, undated (Box 2)
  - Working Class Workshop II, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #11 State and Gov't Tape I, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #11 State and Gov't Tape II, undated (Box 2)
  - Puerto Rican Equality I, undated (Box 2)
  - Puerto Rican Equality II, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #12 Cultural Arena Tape I, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #12 Cultural Arena Tape II, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #15 Developments in Socialist World Tape I, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #15 Developments in Socialist World Tape II, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #8 Peace and Solidarity Tape I, undated (Box 2)
  - Workshop #8 Peace and Solidarity Tape II, undated (Box 2)